/*
[
			{
				"answer": "log on",
				"question": "You need your password to --- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "looking after",
				"question": "It's hard work ------ --- three children all day."
			},
			{
				"answer": "look up",
				"question": "I had to ---- the word --- in a dictionary."
			},
			{
				"answer": "made up",
				"question": "He --- --- some excuse about the dog eating his homework."
			},
			{
				"answer": "moving in",
				"question": "We're ----- --- next week."
			},
			{
				"answer": "pay back",
				"question": "Did you ----- Denise -----?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "pick up",
				"question": "Please --- those toys--- and put them away."
			},
			{
				"answer": "pointed out",
				"question": "He ----- ---- that we had two hours of free time before dinner."
			},
			{
				"answer": "print out",
				"question": "Let me ---- those photographs ---- for you."
			},
			{
				"answer": "pulled off",
				"question": "I --- -- the arm of my sunglasses by mistake."
			},
			{
				"answer": "put away",
				"question": "He --- the notebook --- and stood up."
			},
			{
				"answer": "put back",
				"question": "Can you --- the notebook --- when you've finished with it?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "put down",
				"question": "Emma --- her bag ---- and went upstairs."
			},
			{
				"answer": "put off",
				"question": "Can we --- the meeting --- until tomorrow?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "put on",
				"question": "I don't want to --- -- any more weight!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Put on",
				"question": ".---- your gloves and scarf --- - it's cold outside."
			},
			{
				"answer": "put out",
				"question": "It took three firefighters to --- the fire ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "put up",
				"question": "The teachers will ---- a notice --- about the new courses."
			},
			{
				"answer": "read out",
				"question": "He --- the list of names -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Rip up",
				"question": ".--- -- this piece of paper when you've finished reading it."
			},
			{
				"answer": "rub out",
				"question": "I can't --- it -- because I wrote it in pen."
			},
			{
				"answer": "ran away",
				"question": "The thief -- --- from the police officers."
			},
			{
				"answer": "running out",
				"question": "Many hospitals are ---- ---- of money."
			},
			{
				"answer": "saving up",
				"question": "I'm ---- --- for a new electric guitar."
			},
			{
				"answer": "sent off",
				"question": "It was a very bad foul and the referee -- the player ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "setting off",
				"question": "Go to sleep because we're ---- -- early in the morning."
			},
			{
				"answer": "set up",
				"question": "My dad is going to ---- -- a taxi company."
			},
			{
				"answer": "got away with",
				"question": "They have repeatedly broken the law and ---- --- --- it."
			},
			{
				"answer": "getting into",
				"question": "I hurt my head as I was ----- --- the car."
			},
			{
				"answer": "get off",
				"question": "You need to ---- --- the bus opposite the supermarket."
			},
			{
				"answer": "get on",
				"question": "She seems to -- -- with everybody."
			},
			{
				"answer": "get on",
				"question": "You can buy a ticket when you --- --- the bus."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Get out",
				"question": "Quick! --- -- of the car!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "get over",
				"question": "It can take weeks to --- --- an illness like that."
			},
			{
				"answer": "gets up",
				"question": "He never ---- --- before nine."
			},
			{
				"answer": "giving away",
				"question": "They're --- --- free tickets at the cinema!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "give back",
				"question": "Could you --- my CDs ---- because you've had them for two weeks."
			},
			{
				"answer": "give up",
				"question": "You should ------ --- smoking."
			},
			{
				"answer": "go away",
				"question": "Why don't you just -- --- and leave me alone?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "go back",
				"question": "I can't wait to ---- --- to Italy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "gone off",
				"question": "Has this milk ---- ----?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "go on",
				"question": "Please --- -- with your work while I speak to the head teacher."
			},
			{
				"answer": "going on",
				"question": "There isn't much ---- -- in this town in the evening."
			},
			{
				"answer": "gone out",
				"question": "The fire must have --- -- during the night."
			},
			{
				"answer": "go out",
				"question": "Greg used to --- -- with Katy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "growing up",
				"question": "He rarely saw his father while he was ----- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hang on",
				"question": "Just ---- --- - I'll be ready in a minute."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hang up",
				"question": "The women----- ---their coats and sat down."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hung up",
				"question": "I can't believe that Jessica --- -- without saying goodbye!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "had on",
				"question": "The man --- a strange hat ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hurry up",
				"question": "We haven't got much time, so ---- ---!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "join in",
				"question": "Ask them if you can play - I'm sure they'll let you ---- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "kept out",
				"question": "Cars should be --- -- of the city centre."
			},
			{
				"answer": "leave out",
				"question": "Don't --- your brother --- - let him play with you and your friends."
			},
			{
				"answer": "let down",
				"question": "You've really --- me ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lie down",
				"question": "I'm going to go and ---- --- for a while."
			},
			{
				"answer": "log off",
				"question": "Don't forget to --- -- when you've finished checking your e-mail."
			},
			{
				"answer": "added up",
				"question": "The shop assistant --- -- what I'd bought and told me the total."
			},
			{
				"answer": "blow up",
				"question": "Luckily, the bomb didn't ----- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "broke down",
				"question": "Our car --- --- on the motorway."
			},
			{
				"answer": "broken into",
				"question": "A house in Brecon Place was ---- -- last night."
			},
			{
				"answer": "brought up",
				"question": "She ---- --- three sons on her own."
			},
			{
				"answer": "building up",
				"question": "These exercises are good for ---- -- leg strength."
			},
			{
				"answer": "call back",
				"question": "I'll ---- you --- later when you're not so busy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "called off",
				"question": "The concert has been ----- --- because of the weather."
			},
			{
				"answer": "calmed down",
				"question": "The woman finally ---- --- and explained what happended."
			},
			{
				"answer": "carried on",
				"question": "The phone rang, but Mark just ---- --- watching TV."
			},
			{
				"answer": "catch up",
				"question": "He's missed so much school that he's going to find it hard to --- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cheer up",
				"question": "I started to ---- --- when the sun came out."
			},
			{
				"answer": "clear up",
				"question": "I'll ---- --- if you want to go to bed."
			},
			{
				"answer": "came across",
				"question": "I --- --- a word I'd never seen before."
			},
			{
				"answer": "come back",
				"question": "Give me a call when you -- --- from Greece."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Come on",
				"question": ".----- ---, or we'll be late!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "come out",
				"question": "When does her new book ---- ---?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "cross out",
				"question": "Just --- it --- and rewrite it correctly."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cut down",
				"question": "I'm trying to --- -- on the amount of sugar I eat."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cut off",
				"question": "Pay the electricity bill tomorrow or they might --- us ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cutting off",
				"question": "Keep your roses healthy by ---- ----- any dead flowers."
			},
			{
				"answer": "do up",
				"question": "It's very windy, so --- your coat ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "eat out",
				"question": "Would you like to stay in or ---- ---- tonight?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "fell down",
				"question": "I --- --- and hurt my knee. True"
			},
			{
				"answer": "fallen out",
				"question": "Have you two ---- ---?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "fill in",
				"question": "Just ---- -- this application form, please."
			},
			{
				"answer": "fill up",
				"question": "Just --- this bowl -- with sugar and put it on the table."
			},
			{
				"answer": "find out",
				"question": "I don't want Jerry to --- --- about this."
			},
			{
				"answer": "backs",
				"question": "Beckham --- decisions to drop Rooney."
			},
			{
				"answer": "The latter",
				"question": ".------ accuses the former mismanagement."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lease",
				"question": "We hold an option to extend the ----- for ten more years."
			},
			{
				"answer": "subject of",
				"question": "He's been the ----- multiple documentaries."
			},
			{
				"answer": "granted",
				"question": "Christine O'Donnel ----- an interview to CNN."
			},
			{
				"answer": "definitely",
				"question": "I could ---- write an eight and then a ninth book."
			},
			{
				"answer": "gradually",
				"question": "Bulgaria is ---- pulling out of the crisis."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lately",
				"question": "Have you raided your piggy bank ---?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "obviously",
				"question": "We are ----- pleased to have won by such margin."
			},
			{
				"answer": "particularly",
				"question": "In our society, teachers play a ------ important role."
			},
			{
				"answer": "disprove",
				"question": "It was extremely difficult to ---- her alibi."
			},
			{
				"answer": "argued against",
				"question": "Producers in other countries had ----- giving protected status to Dutch cheese."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Outsourcing",
				"question": ".----- is actually a logical outcome of globalisation"
			},
			{
				"answer": "migration",
				"question": "The author stressed how ----- has benefited Canada."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Competition",
				"question": ".---- is healthy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "inequality",
				"question": "Health ----- between the rich and poor is huge."
			},
			{
				"answer": "stocks",
				"question": "US ----- ended with mixed outcomes on Thursday."
			},
			{
				"answer": "recession",
				"question": "Budged cuts may lead to another ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "unifies",
				"question": "What ---- the students is participating in campus life."
			},
			{
				"answer": "refugees",
				"question": "Residents step up campaign against -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "a steady flow",
				"question": "The future of general avitation depends on ---- of new pilots."
			},
			{
				"answer": "clash",
				"question": "Man shoots himself after --- with officer."
			},
			{
				"answer": "in favour of",
				"question": "Just one person voted --- the elected mayor."
			},
			{
				"answer": "phenomenon",
				"question": "He talked about the ---- of social networking."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Scholar",
				"question": ".----- discovers overlooked Rembrandt in Dutch gallery."
			},
			{
				"answer": "joint ownership",
				"question": "Two of the world's largest sport franchisses will come under ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "issuing shares of stock",
				"question": "Banks have to raise money by ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "sustained economy",
				"question": "The Clinton years provided the best ---- in American history."
			},
			{
				"answer": "conquest",
				"question": "The Norman ---- of southern Italy spanned most of the eleventh century."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Transmission of",
				"question": ".--- both BBC news and CNN television channels was interrupted."
			},
			{
				"answer": "epidemic disease",
				"question": "Hunger and ---- ravaged the survivors"
			},
			{
				"answer": "the plague",
				"question": "She avoids plastic like ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "spices",
				"question": "Buy authentic Indian food and Indian --- here!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "timber",
				"question": "Turnover from ---- exports estimated at $2.43 billion."
			},
			{
				"answer": "widespread",
				"question": "Coyote problem ---- in Calacasieu Parish."
			},
			{
				"answer": "ecology",
				"question": "Seagrasses play an important role in the ---- of coastal waters"
			},
			{
				"answer": "territory",
				"question": "The British used to rule over an amazingly large ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hence",
				"question": "I am unemployed and ---- also very poor."
			},
			{
				"answer": "diverse",
				"question": "Over 70 scientists from ---  countries will take part"
			},
			{
				"answer": "secured",
				"question": "The soldiers ----- the passage through the town."
			},
			{
				"answer": "significant",
				"question": "There is a ---- danger of wildfires."
			},
			{
				"answer": "scrambled for",
				"question": "The driver ---- an explanation, apologising repeatedly."
			},
			{
				"answer": "consent",
				"question": "Users can be added to groups by their Facebook friends without their ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "curiosity",
				"question": "Today was the perfect day to satisfy my .."
			},
			{
				"answer": "longing",
				"question": "Her ---- to be loved ruled her life-"
			},
			{
				"answer": "brought about",
				"question": "The spread of the disease was ----- by infected mosquitoes."
			},
			{
				"answer": "be guided by",
				"question": "The game should ----- the principle of fairness."
			},
			{
				"answer": "subject peoples",
				"question": "Colonies were inhabitated by -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "twain",
				"question": "You have your opinions and I have mine, and never the ---- shall meet."
			},
			{
				"answer": "endured",
				"question": "How many women have ----- rape, and kept quiet."
			},
			{
				"answer": "declines",
				"question": "India's tea export ----- 21.4% in August."
			},
			{
				"answer": "feasible",
				"question": "The company will conduct a study to find out if the City Centre project is  ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "dominion",
				"question": "A ---- is an overseas province of the British Crown."
			},
			{
				"answer": "aspired",
				"question": "Several of France's African colonies ---- to join the Commonwealth."
			},
			{
				"answer": "legacy",
				"question": "John Lennon at 70: His pop culture ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lessen",
				"question": "New drugs can --- symptoms such as memory loss."
			},
			{
				"answer": "the urge to",
				"question": "The youngster felt --- take up Tae Kwon Do."
			},
			{
				"answer": "contagious diseases",
				"question": "Some --- may be passed on throgh pet dogs."
			},
			{
				"answer": "perceives",
				"question": "Changing how a person ---- others is the most effective intervention against loneliness."
			},
			{
				"answer": "securement",
				"question": "Skin --- has always been the final step in surgical procedures."
			},
			{
				"answer": "native population",
				"question": "The Spanish conquest resulted in a rapid reduction of the -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "on site",
				"question": "Our fire station had just one fire engine ---- last night."
			},
			{
				"answer": "external provider",
				"question": "Using an ---------- might be out of question."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cultural affinity",
				"question": "It has a strong ----- with many clients in the region."
			},
			{
				"answer": "rationalised",
				"question": "The tax system should be ----- and be made more user-friendly."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Offshore",
				"question": ".--- outsourcing is growing by blabla per year."
			},
			{
				"answer": "after-sales customer service",
				"question": "We know our ---- is second to none."
			},
			{
				"answer": "acknowledges",
				"question": "The university ----- that mistakes were made."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lack of",
				"question": "Gwyneth Paltrow criticised the ------ quality acting roles offered to women."
			},
			{
				"answer": "core activity",
				"question": "Game drives are the ---- of every safari camp."
			},
			{
				"answer": "talent pool",
				"question": "We are building up a ---- of suitable candidates."
			},
			{
				"answer": "delegated",
				"question": "He had -- his powers to the parliament."
			},
			{
				"answer": "courtesy calls",
				"question": "We regularly make --- to thank our customers for their business."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Deep application integration",
				"question": ".---------=bringing together functions of different computer programmes."
			},
			{
				"answer": "domain specific knowledge",
				"question": "Clients now expect functional expertise and ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "platform work",
				"question": "Google's Android OS has been the focus of new ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "implementation",
				"question": "Schoolwide ---- of a new curriculum will take place in 2017."
			},
			{
				"answer": "intent",
				"question": "The ---- of Facebook Groups is to enhance privacy. (yes, for sure)"
			},
			{
				"answer": "security issue",
				"question": "It has become a national ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "job opportunities",
				"question": "Many websites specialise in offering ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "in turn",
				"question": "She, -----, said that she was only collecting her clothes."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Shaping",
				"question": "Towards 2020: ------ tomorrow's tourism."
			},
			{
				"answer": "pleases",
				"question": "It's very difficult to select a date that ---- everyone."
			},
			{
				"answer": "melting pot",
				"question": "The restaurant is a ---- of cuisines."
			},
			{
				"answer": "supplies",
				"question": "Health officials say flu vaccine ---- are sufficient."
			},
			{
				"answer": "uncomfortable with",
				"question": "Mark feels ------ his own decision."
			},
			{
				"answer": "captured",
				"question": "The gorillas were ----- on film."
			},
			{
				"answer": "loathed",
				"question": "My mum liked him as much as my father ---- him."
			},
			{
				"answer": "uniformity",
				"question": "The court decisions are very much lacking in -----------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "synonymous",
				"question": "The colour pink has become ----- with breast cancer."
			},
			{
				"answer": "insists that",
				"question": "The coach ---- they are building the team."
			},
			{
				"answer": "allegation",
				"question": "I am stunned by the ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Recipients",
				"question": ".----- must prove they need government aid."
			},
			{
				"answer": "repackaged",
				"question": "The company --- its popular Sun Chips in a biodegradable bag."
			},
			{
				"answer": "retransmits",
				"question": "Ivi's service ----- original broadcast streams online."
			},
			{
				"answer": "simplistically",
				"question": "He explained the relativity theory, but very ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "essential to",
				"question": "Vitamin D is  ----- the modern indoor lifestyle."
			},
			{
				"answer": "advantageous for",
				"question": "It is particularly ----- higher-rate taxpayers."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Cartoon Caption",
				"question": "I'd love to win the New Yorker ------ Contest."
			},
			{
				"answer": "complexion",
				"question": "Police described the man as having a dark ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Heterogeneity",
				"question": ".------ is a central characteristic of most cancers."
			},
			{
				"answer": "appeal",
				"question": "Historians restored the cultural ---- of the island."
			},
			{
				"answer": "diverse",
				"question": "Their team reflects the ---- make-up of US society."
			},
			{
				"answer": "crude",
				"question": "Women were routinely subjected to ---- jokes."
			},
			{
				"answer": "intrusive",
				"question": "The background music in the restaurant was -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "embraced",
				"question": "They willingly ---- the new guidelines."
			},
			{
				"answer": "artistically compelling",
				"question": "Which of these pictures is most ------?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "dependence on",
				"question": "We will lower our ---- foreign oil"
			},
			{
				"answer": "line of reasoning",
				"question": "There are problems with his -------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "communication device",
				"question": "Cyberbullying can occur through any -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "expands to",
				"question": "Google Street View ---- Antarctica"
			},
			{
				"answer": "stays in touch with",
				"question": "He still --- his ex-teammates."
			},
			{
				"answer": "became unified",
				"question": "They came togehter as one and -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "apparent",
				"question": "Pelham Police are investigating on ----- suicide."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Insurance company",
				"question": ".------- encourages caution on the road for deer season."
			},
			{
				"answer": "restrictions on",
				"question": "Johnson County places new ---- trash."
			},
			{
				"answer": "fatal crash",
				"question": "Three victims of ---- near Madison identified"
			},
			{
				"answer": "reduced",
				"question": "They are closing their shop so they have ----- the prices."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cost of insurance",
				"question": "Congress was trying to lower the ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "significant",
				"question": "Alamos Gold is expecting a ------ production boost."
			},
			{
				"answer": "landmark",
				"question": "The Matterhorn in Switzerland's most famous -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "stopover point",
				"question": "The hotel is a convenient ------ for business travellers."
			},
			{
				"answer": "spice route",
				"question": ".----=the route from Europe to Asia."
			},
			{
				"answer": "trader",
				"question": ".----- -> to trade with"
			},
			{
				"answer": "legislative",
				"question": "We demand a tax reform in the current -----period."
			},
			{
				"answer": "administrative capital",
				"question": "Pretoria is the ----- of South Africa."
			},
			{
				"answer": "judicial",
				"question": "You should have confidence in your ---- system."
			},
			{
				"answer": "be host to",
				"question": "I want to --- a good --- --- you."
			},
			{
				"answer": "well-suited",
				"question": "This area is ------- to storing natural gas."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Endurance sports",
				"question": ".------ can lead to stress reduction."
			},
			{
				"answer": "manufacturing sector",
				"question": "Globalisatoin led to grave changes in the --------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "constitutional democracy",
				"question": "The USA is a -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "currency",
				"question": "Many countries have adopted the Euro as their ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "racial seperation",
				"question": "Another term for ---- is racial segregation."
			},
			{
				"answer": "plagued",
				"question": "I've been ---- by nightmares recently."
			},
			{
				"answer": "oppressed",
				"question": "For centuries, whites ------ the black majority in South Africa."
			},
			{
				"answer": "a variety of",
				"question": "Werstern supermarkets offer --- large ---- -- products."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Apartheid",
				"question": ".------ in South Africa ended in 1994"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Boers",
				"question": ".----- are the descendants of Dutch-speaking farmers in South Africa."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Afrikaans",
				"question": "The Boer language is called ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Townships",
				"question": ".----- are residential areas for non-whites."
			},
			{
				"answer": "game reserve",
				"question": "You can book tours around the --------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "wildlife",
				"question": "Pollution has an impact on -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "was infected with",
				"question": "He --------- the malaria virus on his last trip."
			},
			{
				"answer": "influential",
				"question": "Her ------ friends helped her get the job."
			},
			{
				"answer": "originate",
				"question": "Where do we ----- from?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "destination",
				"question": "Our ---- this year is Ireland."
			},
			{
				"answer": "reptiles",
				"question": "Caimans are ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "amphibians",
				"question": "The numbers of ----- are declining."
			},
			{
				"answer": "walking safari",
				"question": "A ----- can be arranged if you like."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Hiking trails",
				"question": ".---- lead you through the area."
			},
			{
				"answer": "is unspoilt",
				"question": "The scenery ---- and idyllic."
			},
			{
				"answer": "is unrivalled in",
				"question": "The car --------------- its speed"
			},
			{
				"answer": "flagship",
				"question": "The spaceship was a ----- of Soviet technology."
			},
			{
				"answer": "evident",
				"question": "This is not directly -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "preserve",
				"question": "Let's do our best to ----- this park for our kids."
			},
			{
				"answer": "natural assets",
				"question": "Gas, oil, etc. are -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "unfenced",
				"question": "Large dogs shouldn't be kept -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "free range",
				"question": "The chickens have -----, so they can roam freely."
			},
			{
				"answer": "departs from",
				"question": "The flight ---- Vienna"
			},
			{
				"answer": "riverbed",
				"question": "The ---- was washed out."
			},
			{
				"answer": "communal toilet",
				"question": "We had to share a -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "encounter",
				"question": "The ----- with the lions impressed everyone."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lodges",
				"question": "Whe I travel I prefer hotels to ----. I think they're more comfortable."
			},
			{
				"answer": "convertible",
				"question": "My dad got a red ----- when he retired. He said it was something he had always wanted."
			},
			{
				"answer": "be assured of",
				"question": "You can ------ ------  a wonderful holiday."
			},
			{
				"answer": "sheer",
				"question": "You could see the ---- enjoyment on his face when he got into his new car."
			},
			{
				"answer": "prehistoric sites",
				"question": "There are a lot of ----- to be visited in Ireland."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Plunge",
				"question": ".----- into Vienna's music scene!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "bustling",
				"question": "New York's ----- city centre never sleeps."
			},
			{
				"answer": "laundry",
				"question": "Your ---- is done at the hotel."
			},
			{
				"answer": "dorm",
				"question": "Each ----- has four beds and a bathroom."
			},
			{
				"answer": "room en-suite",
				"question": "All rooms are ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "deposit",
				"question": "You will need to pay a -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "licensed restaurants",
				"question": "In some US states it is almost impossible to find ---- because selling alcohol is prohibited."
			},
			{
				"answer": "On-site",
				"question": ".----- parking is available."
			},
			{
				"answer": "chalet",
				"question": "The view from the ---- is great."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Self-catering",
				"question": ".---- is allowed here."
			},
			{
				"answer": "self-contained",
				"question": "You can rent a ------ cottage in the country"
			},
			{
				"answer": "wheelchair access",
				"question": "Most of the rooms have full -----"
			},
			{
				"answer": "secluded",
				"question": "The area was completely -----. I liked that a lot."
			},
			{
				"answer": "ample",
				"question": "There is ----- room for activities."
			},
			{
				"answer": "ivory",
				"question": "They sell carved wood and small ----- figures."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Peaceful resistance",
				"question": ".---- is a form of non-violent opposition."
			},
			{
				"answer": "go underground",
				"question": "As a political activist he was forced to -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "was compelled to",
				"question": "The minister ----- step down."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Failure to do so",
				"question": ".------ may lead to massive problems."
			},
			{
				"answer": "trial",
				"question": "The murder ------ was in the papers for days."
			},
			{
				"answer": "jail sentence",
				"question": "Finally, the murderer received a lifelong -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "bearer",
				"question": "A passport needs to contain the signature of its -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "annual poll tax",
				"question": ".------=every adult in the community pays this tax."
			},
			{
				"answer": "a tax levied",
				"question": "An income tax is ----- the income ov individuals or businesses."
			},
			{
				"answer": "extended to",
				"question": "The restrictions also ------- really private matters."
			},
			{
				"answer": "are prohibited from",
				"question": "They ---- acting in the play."
			},
			{
				"answer": "persecuted",
				"question": "The Romans ----- the Christians till the beginning of the fourth century."
			},
			{
				"answer": "immobilised",
				"question": "I was temporarily ----- after I had broken my leg."
			},
			{
				"answer": "was deprived of freedom",
				"question": "Mandela ---------- his ----- for over 20 years."
			},
			{
				"answer": "mass resistance to",
				"question": "The government was surprised by the ------ the new law"
			},
			{
				"answer": "armed struggle against",
				"question": "Israel still continues the ------ the Palestinians."
			},
			{
				"answer": "detention",
				"question": "If someone is in -------- they are in jail."
			},
			{
				"answer": "without trial",
				"question": "Mandela was held ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "mood",
				"question": "The ---- of the poem is quite sombre."
			},
			{
				"answer": "free verse",
				"question": "The poem is written in ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "repetition",
				"question": "We don't want a ---- of last year's disaster!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "is mute",
				"question": "A person who ----- is unable to speak. (Hello there!)"
			},
			{
				"answer": "be dumb",
				"question": "See the truth: Don't --- deaf, ----- and blind!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "is chatterbox",
				"question": "She --- an old -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "be talkative/chatty",
				"question": "to -------= to be very communicative"
			},
			{
				"answer": "sitting",
				"question": "The story is not long. You can read it in one ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "casually",
				"question": "She ----- mentioned her pregnancy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "traumatic incident",
				"question": "After the ----- she needed therapy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "tap",
				"question": "In some countries you shouldn't drink ---- water."
			},
			{
				"answer": "burst into",
				"question": "The police ----- the flat."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lounges",
				"question": "Most airport ----- aren't open to everyone."
			},
			{
				"answer": "stained",
				"question": "Tea had ----- the tabletop."
			},
			{
				"answer": "verendah",
				"question": "The wide ----- offers great views."
			},
			{
				"answer": "patrolling the streets",
				"question": "Because of all the break-ins more police are ------- now."
			},
			{
				"answer": "suspicious",
				"question": "This seems ----- to me."
			},
			{
				"answer": "dejectedly",
				"question": "He left the meeting ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "vomit",
				"question": ".------ -> to throw up"
			},
			{
				"answer": "dial",
				"question": "Please ---- 911 in case of an emergency."
			},
			{
				"answer": "rigid",
				"question": "When she heard the news, she went stiff and ----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "was scared stiff",
				"question": "I ------ when I heard the window break."
			},
			{
				"answer": "emigrate",
				"question": "Many people were forced to -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "longing for",
				"question": "I'm ------ a hot cup of tea now."
			},
			{
				"answer": "veld",
				"question": "In the middle of the ---- is an old monastery."
			},
			{
				"answer": "snapped from",
				"question": "Her neck almost ----- all the weight."
			},
			{
				"answer": "mascara",
				"question": "Often really expensive ---- looks like any other."
			},
			{
				"answer": "become used to",
				"question": "My uncle has ---- his new life abroad."
			},
			{
				"answer": "sigh",
				"question": "He stood up with a ---- of relief."
			},
			{
				"answer": "eyelashes",
				"question": "Many people find long (---)----- very attractive"
			},
			{
				"answer": "fluttered",
				"question": "The butterfly ---- over the flower."
			},
			{
				"answer": "utter",
				"question": "In many regimes, people don't dare to ---- any criticism."
			},
			{
				"answer": "long drawn-out",
				"question": "It's a ------- process."
			},
			{
				"answer": "bare",
				"question": "You shouldn't enter this church with ---- arms."
			},
			{
				"answer": "I can't help it",
				"question": "I'm addicted to soap operas. ----------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "unbearable",
				"question": "We all suffered in the ----- African heat."
			},
			{
				"answer": "streamed out of",
				"question": "Gas -------- a leckage."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Gargling noises",
				"question": ".------- came out of the bathroom."
			},
			{
				"answer": "rattling noises",
				"question": "A rattlesnake warns with -------- before attacking."
			},
			{
				"answer": "stocky",
				"question": "These sizes are for ---- men."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hissing",
				"question": "It's a language with many ---- sounds."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Steam irons",
				"question": ".----- are much more handy than regular ones."
			},
			{
				"answer": "mumbled",
				"question": "He ---- something and disappeared into the crowd."
			},
			{
				"answer": "clutched onto",
				"question": "I ----- my seat as the plane took off."
			},
			{
				"answer": "burglar bars",
				"question": "They had extra thick -------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "vicious",
				"question": "Poisonous snakes aren't ----, they just want to survive."
			},
			{
				"answer": "are worked up",
				"question": "What happened? What ---- you so ----- about?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "glared at",
				"question": "I ------ our cat angrily."
			},
			{
				"answer": "black kohl",
				"question": "To my mind, she always puts on too much ---- ---."
			},
			{
				"answer": "canopy",
				"question": "As soon as spring comes, we sit under our ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "pavement",
				"question": "Make sure you keep the dog on the -----!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "scrape",
				"question": "Mum always uses a special stone to ---- her feet soft."
			},
			{
				"answer": "soles",
				"question": "My shoes have rubber ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "thorns",
				"question": "Watch out, that bush has long -----!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "driveway",
				"question": "A ------ leads you to the house."
			},
			{
				"answer": "lawn mower",
				"question": "My ----- has broken down. May I borrow yours?"
			},
			{
				"answer": "humming",
				"question": "The concert really got the crowd --------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "suburbs",
				"question": "I live in one of Vienna's -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "barrier",
				"question": ".------- = limit, border, boundary"
			},
			{
				"answer": "Washing lines",
				"question": ".----- come in all kinds of lengths and colours."
			},
			{
				"answer": "vest",
				"question": "You'll find your life ----- under your seat."
			},
			{
				"answer": "estate agent",
				"question": "Selling your house through an ------ is easier."
			},
			{
				"answer": "slops",
				"question": "I can't find my -----. Maybe I left them by the pool again."
			},
			{
				"answer": "bellowing",
				"question": "I know that your team won, but stop ------ right now!"
			},
			{
				"answer": "A hoarse rattle",
				"question": "I couldn't speak. ---------------- was all that I managed."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Laryngitis",
				"question": ".----- is an inflammation of the voice box (=larynx)"
			},
			{
				"answer": "cupped",
				"question": "Her hands ------ the candle to protecto it from the wind."
			},
			{
				"answer": "A bunch of keys",
				"question": ".------- was found in the men's restroom."
			},
			{
				"answer": "let go of",
				"question": "I love her so much; I cannot ----- her."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cling on to",
				"question": "We all ------ life."
			},
			{
				"answer": "profound",
				"question": "His general knowledge is -------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "overwhelmed",
				"question": "I am ----- with joy."
			},
			{
				"answer": "hugged",
				"question": "We ----- for a long time before she got on the train."
			},
			{
				"answer": "tearstained",
				"question": "Any idea what's wrong with Sue? She looks ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "cute",
				"question": "That dog is so ------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "breathy rattle",
				"question": "Her laugh is a -------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "smudged",
				"question": "Mum's lipstick is -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "teasingly",
				"question": "My sister held the piece of cake under my nose ---------."
			},
			{
				"answer": "dripped from",
				"question": "Tears ----- her eyes."
			},
			{
				"answer": "are traumatised",
				"question": "Children --- often ---- by their parents' divorce."
			},
			{
				"answer": "forced himself to",
				"question": "After his heart attack he ----- lose weight."
			},
			{
				"answer": "work through",
				"question": "It took her years to ----- the loss of her husband."
			},
			{
				"answer": "narrative points of view",
				"question": "Standard ---- are first person, third person or omniscient."
			},
			{
				"answer": "merit",
				"question": "His ----- is the reunification of the country."
			},
			{
				"answer": "provided",
				"question": "Dogs are permitted ---- that they are house-trained."
			},
			{
				"answer": "articulate",
				"question": "She didn't dare to ----- any criticism."
			},
			{
				"answer": "released",
				"question": "Three political prisoners were -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "momentum",
				"question": "A large part of the political ---- comes from the oppressed themselves."
			},
			{
				"answer": "catalyst",
				"question": "Mandela functioned as a -----."
			},
			{
				"answer": "economic",
				"question": "There are ---- reasons for closing the factory."
			},
			{
				"answer": "Embargoes",
				"question": ".----- that were imposed on South Africa helped to end Apartheid."
			}
		]
		*/
		[
			{
			  "answer": "genius",
			  "question": "M. Alcott claimed that talent wasn't -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "inspiration",
			  "question": "He is real ----- to me."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Perspiration",
			  "question": ".----- is regulated by the nervous system."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "light bulb",
			  "question": "The ---- on the ceiling flickered and went out."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Accordingly",
			  "question": ".-------, we cannot accept that."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "skip school",
			  "question": "Many students who ---- regularly say they find lessons boring."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "deadline",
			  "question": "The ---- is next Monday."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "absorbing",
			  "question": "The project is so ----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "salary",
			  "question": "The yearly ---- he was offered by our competitior made him leave our company."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "over-achiever",
			  "question": "I am not an ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "goes the extra mile",
			  "question": "Bob always ----- when studying for tests."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "exceeded my own expectations",
			  "question": "When I finished the project I ----------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "chilling out",
			  "question": "I prefer ----- to working out."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "work out",
			  "question": "to -----= to exercise, to practise sports"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "animator",
			  "question": "He always dreamed of working as an ----- in L.A."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "vital",
			  "question": "Patience is ---- if you want to become a doctor."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "trustworthy",
			  "question": "We are looking for a ---- driver."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "reliable",
			  "question": "We are looking for a ---- and kind household help."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "carvers",
			  "question": "Some --- use wood as well as stone for their work."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "globetrotter",
			  "question": "My cousin's a real --------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "employer",
			  "question": "My ---- is Dr Smith."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "school leaver",
			  "question": "Every ---- should get a job."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "ability to learn",
			  "question": ".------ = to be able to learn. (what an amazing explanation)"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Teamwork",
			  "question": ".---- is becoming more and more important."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Self-management",
			  "question": ".------ is an important skill in the workplace."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "initiative",
			  "question": "It was on his --- that they started the project."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "enterprise",
			  "question": "Google has turned into a multinational -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "employable",
			  "question": "How ---- are you?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Employees",
			  "question": ".----- of the firm about to be closed went on strike."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "provide information",
			  "question": "If you'd like me to invest in your project you need to ----- more ---- first."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "carry out instructions",
			  "question": "Don't wait to be told to ------. Show some initiative!"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "standing around",
			  "question": "Don't let the boss see you ---- doing nothing."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "to be told what to do",
			  "question": "She always needs to --------. I wish she would show more initiative."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "adjust work procedures",
			  "question": "In your new job you will have to ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "take action",
			  "question": "You will also have to ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "According to",
			  "question": ".----- the rules you'll have to wear a suit and tie."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "time frame",
			  "question": "It is important that you stay within the ----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "ensure",
			  "question": "Please ----- that you are on time."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "efficiently",
			  "question": "Doing things ----- is doing things right."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "effectively",
			  "question": "Doing things ----- is doing the right things."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "rely on",
			  "question": "You can always ---- me."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Updating one's knowledge",
			  "question": ".----- is essential in every life phase."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Adapting to changes",
			  "question": ".------ gets harder when you get older."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "is experienced in",
			  "question": "She ----- leading projects."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "am skilled at",
			  "question": "I ------ new technologies."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "gain an understanding of",
			  "question": "He tries to ----- the complex process."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "develop my strengths",
			  "question": "I try to ---- in computing."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "widens my horizon",
			  "question": "I find that travelling really --------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "fetch",
			  "question": "One moment, I'll --- him."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "hang on a moment",
			  "question": "Please, ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "extension",
			  "question": "Ms Herbert's ------ is 405."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "put through",
			  "question": "I'll --- you --- to Mr Kline"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "hold the line",
			  "question": "Could you please ------?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "is not available",
			  "question": "Sorry, she -------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "engaged",
			  "question": "Sorry, the line is -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "enquire about",
			  "question": "Please ----- the departure details."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "ring back later",
			  "question": "Sure, no problem. I will -------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "convenient",
			  "question": "What time would be ---------?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "reception",
			  "question": "The --- in this valley is really bad."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "was cut off",
			  "question": "Sorry, the line -------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "speak up a bit",
			  "question": "Excuse me, could you -------?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "bear with me for a moment",
			  "question": "I would ask you to ------ me --------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "fire away",
			  "question": "OK, please ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "VAT",
			  "question": "How much ---- do you have to pay in the US?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "invoice",
			  "question": "Please send the ---- back to us."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "accounts department",
			  "question": "He works in the ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "minutes",
			  "question": "Who is writing the ---- today?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "private purposes",
			  "question": "School computers must not be used for -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "meeting scheduled",
			  "question": "The ---- is --- for Wednesday."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "postponed",
			  "question": "Our boss was late, so the meeting had to be -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "connectives",
			  "question": "However, but, etc. are ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "monotonous",
			  "question": "His voice is -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "address the audience",
			  "question": "You should ---- directly and not talk to yourself."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Involve",
			  "question": ".----- people from the audience!"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "corporate culture",
			  "question": "Their ---- is a disaster."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "enhance",
			  "question": "You should ---- your training schemes further."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "core values",
			  "question": "The ---- of our company are summarised in that folder."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "hierarchy",
			  "question": "There's no ---- among us students, I guess."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "collaborative environment",
			  "question": "Our aim is to create a rich -------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "integrity",
			  "question": "One's personal ---- should never be violated."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "accesible",
			  "question": "The university has made ist library more ----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "is related to",
			  "question": "This problem --- closely ----- one we already had."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "hires",
			  "question": "This company ----- around 20 new employees a year."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "traits",
			  "question": "His character ---- are very positive."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "flexible",
			  "question": "Today workers have to be ---- and adaptable."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "adaptable",
			  "question": "His team is highly ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "determine",
			  "question": "It's not easy to ----- the causes."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Academics",
			  "question": ".---- are much more important to him than sports."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "credentials",
			  "question": "Her ----- are extraordinary."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "theoretical",
			  "question": "This is just a ---- question."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Obviously",
			  "question": ".--- something went wrong."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "annual",
			  "question": "We have a --- family meeting."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "stock options",
			  "question": "Some companies offer ----- to their employees."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "increase salaries",
			  "question": "to ----- != to decrease salaries"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "perk",
			  "question": ".---- = benefit, advantage"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "headquarters",
			  "question": "The UN ----- is/are in New York."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "work-life balance",
			  "question": "We all want to achieve a better --------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "paternity leave",
			  "question": "More men take the chance to go on ----- now."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "spouse",
			  "question": "The president will visit China with his -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "reimburse",
			  "question": "We ---- you 90$ if you buy that TV."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Hybrid cars",
			  "question": ".--- are becoming more popular."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "shuttle service",
			  "question": "The hotel has a ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "commuters",
			  "question": "In the morning the trains are always full of -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "wage",
			  "question": "The minimum ----- is 7.25 $ an hour."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "White-collar workers",
			  "question": ".------- have office jobs."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "blue-collar worker",
			  "question": "He used to be a ------, but now he works at an office."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "career development",
			  "question": "What's your ----- plan?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "skills training",
			  "question": "Language ---- includes listening, writing, etc."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "available on call",
			  "question": "Our staff is ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "linguistic skills",
			  "question": "We are looking for a communicative person with highly developed -------. (so probably not me)"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "assessment procedures",
			  "question": "The new ----- will be explained soon."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "social skills",
			  "question": "His ---- are exellent."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "reputation",
			  "question": "This company has a bad ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "chair the meeting",
			  "question": "This year Mr Carmona will ----- at the conference."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "take the minutes",
			  "question": "Are you sure it's really my turn to ---- again?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "agenda",
			  "question": "What's on the ----- today?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "subsidiaries",
			  "question": "Siemens has worldwide -------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "executive board",
			  "question": "The ---- has agreed."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "liberal",
			  "question": "Google and Microsoft have very ---- corporate cultures."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "labour force",
			  "question": "The Austrian ----- is generally well qualified."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Relocation",
			  "question": ".----- of manufacturing towards the East is quite common these days."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "abolition",
			  "question": "We will not support the ----- of time recording."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Overtime",
			  "question": ".---- pay is regulated individually."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Time recording",
			  "question": ".---- of workers has become quite common."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "company premises",
			  "question": "Entrance to the ------ is not allowed."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "re on first name terms",
			  "question": "I'm glad we'---------. It's a lot less formal."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "ruthless",
			  "question": "He proved to be a ----- driver."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "insensitivity",
			  "question": "It's difficult for me to tolerate -----."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "fierce",
			  "question": "There was a --- opposition to the cutbacks."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "cut cost",
			  "question": "Managers said they needed to ---- by up to 30%."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "consider",
			  "question": "Please ----- the fact that this is impossible to me."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "walking distance",
			  "question": "It's within ------."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "drudgery",
			  "question": "The invention of the washing machine has helped me to lessen  the ---- of housework immensely."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "fades",
			  "question": "Our childhood ----- in our memory."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "futurologists",
			  "question": "What are the views of -----?"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "exodus",
			  "question": "In Europe there is an ------ of young scientists to the US."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "blurred",
			  "question": "verschwimmen"
			},
			{
			  "answer": "drew up",
			  "question": "We quickly ----- a plan to get out of this mess."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "Cyber attacks",
			  "question": ".---- on hospitals are a real danger to patients."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "hologram",
			  "question": "A ---- is a 3D image on a 2D surface."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "polarisation",
			  "question": "There is a deep ---- between political parties."
			},
			{
			  "answer": "proliferation",
			  "question": "The --- of nuclear weapons should be stopped."
			}
		  ]
